Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art public programs records, circa 1995-2011 COR0003.5.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Program files, financial records, and calendar productions, 1994-2011; Series 1
  - Film Director's - Grant, 2000 March 6; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Illustrators Series, 2000 March - 2000 April; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Film Directors - Haines, 2000 March 20; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Film Directors - Pollck, 2000 March 27; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Film Directors - Schlesinger, 2000 April 5; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Walter Denny - Topkapie, 2000 March 14; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Arnold Newman, 2000 March 16; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Mom's Mabley, 2000 March 26; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Paige Rense - Off-Site Cancelled, 2000 March 29; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Ibero-American Concert Series #5, 2000 March 30; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - April 17 FY2000 Old Masters Lect., Circa 2000; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - 2000 April PP Cal FY2000, Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - April 3 FY2000 Joan Nathan, 2000 April 3; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - April 2 FY2000, 2000 April 2; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - April 6 FY2000 Ibero-American Concert Series #7, 2000 April 6; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Illustrater Series, Circa 2000; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Sept. 25, Nov, 13, February 19, April 8 FY2000 Washington Chamber Symphony, 2000 September-April; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - April 9 FY2000 New Danish Saxophone, 2000 April 9; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - April 11 FY2000 William Brumfield, 2000 April 11; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Contemporary Music Forum FY2000 Oct 7, Nov 11, Dec 16, Feb 3, Mar 2, Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - P404 April 20 FY2000 Hungarian Concert, 2000 April 20; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - 2000 May PP Cal FY2000, Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - May 8 FY2000 Elaine Kurtz, 2000 May 8; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Topkapi 1999, Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - May 2 FY2000 William Adair, 2000 May 2; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - May 4 FY2000 Ibero-American Concert Series #8, 2000 May 4; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - April 10 FY2000 NGA/Hirsh. Tour, 2000 April 10; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Indonesian Embassy November 16 FY2001, 2001 November 16; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - April 26 FY2000 Du Pont Estate, 2000 April 26; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - April 30 FY2000 Topkapi Concert, 2000 April 30; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - May 3 FY2000 Turkish Dancers, 2000 May 3; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - May 6 FY2000 Greek Society, 2000 May 6; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - May 10 FY2000 Embassy Row Walking Tour, 2000 May 10; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - May 10 FY2000 The Ebsworth Collection, 2000 May 10; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - May 11 FY2000 Lithuanian Concert, 2000 May 11; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - May 15 FY2000 Joe Nierman, 2000 May 15; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - May 16 FY2000 Sunny Sumter, 2000 May 16; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - May 17 FY2000 Space Framed, 2000 May 17; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - May 18 FY2000 Collage Dance Group, 2000 May 18; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - May 18 FY2000 Allan Stypeck, 2000 May 18; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - May 23 FY2000 Topkapi The Movie w/ Dr. Atil, 2000 May 23; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - May 25 FY2000 Richard Rashke Play, 2000 May 25; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - May 27 FY2000 Washington Storytellers Theatre, 2000 May 27; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - June 6 FY2000 John Eaton, 2000 June 6; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - June 8 FY2000 Ibero-American Concert Series #9 CANCELLED, 2000 June 8; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - June 14 FY2000 Eleanor Carucci CANCELLED, 2000 June 14; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - June 13 FY2000 Modernism Talk CANCELLED, 2000 June 13; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - June 1 FY2000 Jenny Lind Concert, 2000 June 1; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - June 4 FY2000 Tribute to Charlie Byrd, 2000 June 4; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - June 7 FY2000 International Court Walking, 2000 June 7; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - June 8 FY2000 Ian Schrager, 2000 June 8; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - June 12 FY2000 Jerry Whiddon, 2000 June 12; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - June 19 FY2000 Charles Guggenheim, 2000 June 19; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - June 27 Sarah Rossbach FY2000, 2000 June 27; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - June 28 FY2000 Art in the White House, 2000 June 28; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - June 29 FY2000 Deborah Soloman on Rockwell, 2000 June 29; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - 2000 July PP Cal FY2001, Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - July 6 Justine Parsons FY2001, 2001 July 6; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - July 11 FY2001 John Eaton, 2001 July 11; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - July 13 FY2001 Robin Givan, 2001 July 13; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - July 14 FY2001 Sam Harry's Evening, 2001 July 14; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - July 16 FY2001 Satin Doll Trio, 2001 July 16; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - July 19 FY2001 Rockwell Sitters!, 2001 July 19; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - NYC Trip FY2000 July 21, Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - July 26 FY2001 Rockwell: Laura Claridge, 2001 July 26; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - July 27 FY2001 Americans in Paris (McDonald), 2001 July 27; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - July 31 FY2001 Tom Head_Washingtonian, 2001 July 31; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - September 15 FY2001 Sam Harry's CANCELLED, 2001 September 15; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - September 27 FY2001 Classical Cambodian Dance, 2001 September 27; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - September 7 FY2001 Suitable for Today, 2001 September 7; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - September 11 Fy2001 John Eaton, 2001 September 11; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Sept 12 FY2001 Peru Residence, 2001 September 12; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Sept 14 FY2001 Mark Leach - Sitter, 2001 September 14; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Sept 18 FY2001 Juliet Taylor - Arch Cambell, 2001 September 18; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - September 19 FY2001 Allie Bowling, 2001 September 19; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Sept 20 FY2001 International Court (2), 2001 September 20; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Sept 24 FY2001 Johansen Intern. Competition, 2001 September 24; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Gillian Humphrey's FY2001 Sept 25, 2001 September 25; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Sept 26 FY2001 Architecture w/ Marafat, 2001 September 26; Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Oct. FY2001 Ford's Theatre Inherit, 2001 October 1; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Oct. 2 FY2001 Window Dressing, 2001 October 2; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Oct. 4 FY2001 Family Treasures, 2001 October 4; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Sept 13 / Oct. 6 FY01 Faberge, 2001 September-October; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Oct 10 FY2001 Steve Ross, 2001 October 10; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Oct. 11 FY2001 Art Nouveau-Paul Greenhalgh, 2001 October 11; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - October 16 FY2001 Mindy Weisel, 2001 October 16; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - October 15 FY2001 Danish Jazz Group, 2001 October 15; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Architecture with Mina FY2001 L455a,b,c,d,e Sept. 26, Oct. 3,17,23,24, 2001 September-October; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Oct. 21 FY2001 Fashion Trip - NYC, 2001 October 21; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - October 23 FY2001 Twyla Tharp, 2001 October 23; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Oct. 26 FY2001 Rachel Kaplam-Rome, 2001 October 26; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - November 1 FY2001 Galileo, 2001 November 1; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - November 2 FY2001 Ralph Gibson, 2001 November 2; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - November 6 FY2001 Spanish Emb. Musicians, 2001 November 6; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - November 8 FY2001 Ethelburt Miller, 2001 November 8; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - November FY2001 13 Inge Morath, 2001 November 13; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Nov. 14 FY2001 Hearst Castle, 2001 November 14; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - November 15 FY2001 Arena Stage, Play On!, 2001 November 15; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - November 19 FY2001 May Knott, 2001 November 19; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - November 20 FY2001 Alexandra La Pierre, 2001 November 20; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - November 28 FY2001 Andromeda Shack, 2001 November 28; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - November 30 FY2001 Marlene Ver Plank, 2001 November 30; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - December 3 FY2001 Computer Music CANCELLED, 2001 December 3; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - December 4 FY2001 Columbian Embassy Music, 2001 December 4; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - December 5 FY2001 Kitty Kelley, 2001 December 5; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - December 11 FY2001 Deian McBride, 2001 December 11; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - December 12 FY2001 Warhol Film/lec. FY2001, 2001 December 12; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Larry Kirkland 25 yrs., Circa 2001; Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Loose Papers, Circa 2001; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - January 9 FY2001 Tiffany Book, 2001 January 9; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - January 11 FY2001 Ivan Karp CANCELLED, 2001 January 11; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - January 24 FY2001 Baby Jane Holzer CANCELLED, 2001 January 24; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - January 28 FY2001 Steve Reich CANCELLED, 2001 January 28; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - January 31 FY2001 GW Facility Rental, 2001 January 31; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - January 16 FY2001 Scott Simon, 2001 January 16; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - January 17 FY2001 Ziva Spanish Dance, 2001 January 17; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - January 22 FY2001 Tom Sistesma, 2001 January 22; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - January 22 FY2002 Blues in the Night / Arena Stage, 2002 January 22; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - January 23 FY2001 Pam Bricker, 2001 January 23; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - January 25 FY2001 Nick Olcott, 2001 January 25; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - January 27 FY2001 Mozart's B'day / In Series, 2001 January 27; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - February 12 FY2001 Shimon Attie CANCELLED, 2001 February 12; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - February 5 FY2001 Five Guitar Tribute-Byrd, 2001 February 5; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - February 7 FY2001 Ralph Appelbaum, 2001 February 7; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - February 8 FY2001 Wayne Thiebaud, 2001 February 8; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Oct. 29, Feb. 18 FY2001 Violins of Lafayette, 2001 October-February; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - February 21,28, 3/7,21 1st Ladies of Stage FY2001, 2001 February-March; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Jane Alexander, Circa 2001; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - February 26 FY2001 Betty Monkman, 2001 February 26; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - February 27 FY2001 Matisse, 2001 February 27; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Cherry Jones, 2001 February 28; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Loose Public Programs Documents, 2001 March; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Caucus Room Cancelled, 2001 March 23; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Richard Brown, 2001 March 5; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Patti Lupone, 2001 March 7; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Ibero-American/Honduras, 2001 March 8; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Hillwood Museum, 2001 March 14; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Film Festival/Andy Goldsworthy, 2001 March 19; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Scandanavian Design, 2001 March 20; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Zoe Caldwell, 2001 March 21; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Suzannee Farrell, 2001 March 22; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Carribean Jazz Ensemble, 2001 March 28; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Loose Public Programs Documents, 2001 April; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Ivan MacDonald, 2001 April 2; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Religious Edifices Tour, 2001 April 3; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Contemporary Music Forum, 2001 December 7; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Beckett Radio Plays, 2001 April 10; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Marion McEvoy, 2001 April 11; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Lithuanian Embassy Music, 2001 April 17; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Illustrators Series, 2001 March - 2001 April; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Ibero-American Series Ecuador, 2001 April 26; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Washington Chamber Symphony, 2001; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - In Series Operetta, 2001 April; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Dave Anderson Quartet, 2001 April 30; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Loose Public Programs Documents, 2001 May; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Judith Jameson Cancelled, 2001 May 3; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Mark Stevens, 2001 May 2; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Tour to Baltimore, 2001 May 4; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Steichen Book, 2001 May 7; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Mexican Cooking, 2001 April; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Jan Greenberg on Gehry, 2001 May 10; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Ride Down Mt. Morgan, 2001 May; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Octogon House, 2001 May 16; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Tour of Dumbarton Oaks, 2001 May 17; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Tour to NYC Jackie O, 2001 May 19; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Just a Woman, 2001 May 21; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Art Deco in D.C., 2001 May 22; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Ibero-American Series-Paraguay, 2001 May 31; Series 1 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Correspondences, 2001; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - CGA June 2001 Night Day, 2001 June; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - June 20 FY2001 Young and Rollins CANCELLED, 2001 June 20; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - June 23 Fy2001 Tour to Charlottesville, 2001 June 23; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - June 5 FY2001 Martine van Hamel, 2001 June 5; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - June 6 FY2001 Jenny Lind Concert, 2001 June 6; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - June 7 FY2001 Jim Polshek, 2001 June 7; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - June 11 / June 15 FY2001 State Depart. Rooms Lecture, 2001 June 11-15; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - June 12 FY2001 Chinese art / Architecture, 2001 June 12; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - June 13 FY2001 Rob Levit Ensemble, 2001 June 13; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - June 14 FY2001 The Fearless Shopper, 2001 June 14; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - June 18 FY2001 Celeste Holm, 2001 June 18; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - June 21 FY2001 Native American Art-West, 2001 June 21; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - June 25 FY2001 Dinner at D.C. Coast, 2001 June 25; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - June 29, 2001, 2001 June 29; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - CGA July 2000 Night Day, 2000 July; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Italian Architecture FY2002 July 9, 10, Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Unified Jazz Ensemble FY2002 July 17 CANCELED, Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - NYC Tour July 12th 2001, 2001 July 12; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Persian Music FY2002 July 12, Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Anna Bergman Fy2002 July 16, 2002 Juuly 16; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Fallingwater FY2002 July 18, Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Peru Residence FY2001 July 19, Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Phyllis Richman S, 2002 July 24; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Michael York FY2002 July 26, Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - July 30 FY2001 Ibero-American; Mexico, 2001 July 30; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - L558 Brown-Davis Designs FY2002 July 31, Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Home Design Magazine Summer 2001, Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - CGA Sept. 2001 Night Day, 2001 September; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Saks Jandel FY2002 September 13, Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Ambassador J. Edsel Edmunds FY2002 September 9, Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Flora Iacchia FY2002 September 12, 2001, 2001 September 12; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Blake Gopnik FY2002 September 19, Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - John Eaton FY2002 September 23, 2002 Septmeber 23; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Leslie Cockburn FY2002 September 24, Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Embassy Walking Tour FY2002 September 25, Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Indonesian Embassy FY2002 October 4 CANCELED, Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Michael Kahn FY2002 October 3, Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Bill Christenberry FY2002 October 8, Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Ford's Theatre / To Kill A Mockingbird FY2002 October 10, Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - In Series FY2002 October 12, December 2, 2002 October-December; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Icelandic Embassy FY2002 October 14, Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Michael Kaiser FY2002 October 16, Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Will Faulkner FY2002 October 22, Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Caudian Embassy FY2002 October 29, Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Annie Cohen-Solal, FY2002 Painting American October 30, 2002 October 30; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Bach Consort FY2002 November 3, Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Gerry Arpino November 8 FY2002, 2002 November 8; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Le Grand Fromage November 6 FY2002, 2002 November 6; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - November 6 FY2002 Embassy of Romania, 2002 November 6; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Deborah Tannen FY2002 November 7, Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Embassy Walking Tour FY2002 November 9, Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Margaret Russell FY2002 November 12 CANCELED, Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Thomas Eakins FY2002 Oct. 24 / Nov. 13, 2002 October-November; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Steve Ross FY2002 November 14, Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Danse Orientale FY2002 November 26, Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Nov. 27 FY2002 Ibero-American Series, 2002 November 27; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Andy Grundberg FY2002 November 29, Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Loose Newspaper Articles 2001, Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - [Public Programs Oct.-Dec. 2001], 2001 October-December; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - In Series / Joyful Tidings: Background Gospel FY2002 December 2, Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - December 3 FY2002 Marjone Venit, 2002 December 3; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Embassy of Norway Rental FY2002 Tuesday, Dec. 4, 2002 December 4; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - December 5 FY2002 Scena Theatre, 2002 December 5; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - December 6 FY2002 Embassy of Poland, 2002 December 6; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - New York Holiday Bus Tour FY2002 Dec 5, 2001, 2001 December 5; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - December 9 FY2002 Sattin Doll Trio, 2002 December 9; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - December 16 FY2002 Ibero-American Series:Spain FY2002, 2002 December 16; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - December 10 FY2002 World Movement Fund, 2002 December 10; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - January 10 FY2002 Alexander Tselyakov, 2002 January 10; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - January 15 FY2002 Landscape Architecture Series: Ignacio Bunster, 2002 January 15; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - January 14 Cabo FY2002, 2002 January 14; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - January 16 FY2002 Ziva's Spanish Dance Ensemble, 2002 January 16; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - January 17 FY2002 The Lure of Oriental Carpets, 2002 January 17; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - January 23 FY2002 Rachel Cartey, 2002 January 23; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - January 24 FY2002 Ron Holloway, 2002 January 24; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - January 27 Fy2002 May Knott, 2002 January 27; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - January 28, 2002 Jorge Solis, 2002 January 28; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - January 29 FY2002 Landscape Architecture Series: James van Sweden, 2002 January 29; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - January 30 FY2002 Septine Webre, 2002 January 30; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - January 31 FY2002 Jack Cowart, 2002 January 31; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Feb. 26 - Peru Fy2002 Ibero American Series CANCELED, 2002 February 26; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - February 5 FY2002 Landscape Architecture Series: Carol Franklin, 2002 February 5; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - February 6 FY2002 Havanna Select, 2002 February 6; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - February 7 FY2002 Becoming Mona Lisa / Donald Sassoon, 2002 February 7; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - February 11 FY2002 Persian Classical Music, 2002 February 11; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - February 12 FY2002 Fords/ I'm Not Rappaport, 2002 February 12; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - February 13 FY2001 Theatre Bonanza, 2001 February 13; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - February 27 FY2002 Black Gal Needin' To Be Loved, 2002 February 27; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - February 28 FY2002 Indonesian Embassy, 2002 February 28; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Public Programs Jan.-Feb. 2002, 2002 January-February; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - March 7 FY2002 Romanian Jazz, 2002 March 7; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - March 12 FY2002 Dinner at Maxim, 2002 March 12; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - March 14 FY2002 Gina Caruso "The World is in My Arms", 2002 March 14; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - March 17 FY2002 Jorie Graham, 2002 March 17; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - March 18 FY2002 Environmental Film Festival, 2002 March 18; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - March 19 FY2002 Patrick Clerkin Lilian O'Connell, 2002 March 19; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - March 20 April 12 FY2002 Marcel Wanders, 2002 March 20-April 12; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - March 23 Fy2002 Carmen Marc valvo at Neiman Marcus, 2002 March 23; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - March 25 FY2002 Washington Ballet, 2002 March 25; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Dutch Design March-April 2002, 2002 March-April; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - March 26 FY2002 Suzanne Bauman, 2002 March 26; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - March 21 FY2002 Jeff Koons, 2002 March 21; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - March 28 FY2002 Ibero American Series: Paraguay, 2002 Marrch 28; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Corcoran Public Programs April 2002, 2002 April; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - PSA Washington Chamber Symphony FY2002 A,B,C,D Sept. 22, Jan. 19, Feb. 23, Apr. 6, 2002 January-September; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Leading Ladies - Bernadette Peters CANCELLED, Circa 2002; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Leading Ladiees FY2002, Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - April 15 FY2002 Charlotte Ford, 2002 April 15; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - April 12 Shirley Jones FY2002, 2002 April 12; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - April 11 FY2002 An Evening with Edith Piaf, 2002 April 11; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - April 12 FY2002 Panel and Reception at Dutch Emb., 2002 April 12; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - April 17 FY2002 Embassy Row Walking Tour, 2002 April 17; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - April 17 FY2002 Leading Ladies - Elizabeth Ashley, 2002 April 17; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - April 18 FY2002 Pete Souza - WHNPA Series, 2002 April 18; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - April 23 FY2002 Steve May - Goya, 2002 April 23; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - April 25 FY2002 Pamela Clarke Keogh - Jackie Style, 2002 April 25; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - April 29 FY2002 Charisma, 2002 April 29; Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Loose Public Programs Press, 2002 May; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Night Day Drafts, 2002 May; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - May 2002 Calendar, 2002 May; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Anna Bergman, 2002 May 1; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Garden Tour, 2001 May 1; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Ibero American Series: Ecuador, 2002 May 7; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Contemporary Music Forum, 2002; Series 1 (Box 34, Folder 7)